let savollar2 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "adventure",
        answer: "B. sarguzasht",
        options: [
            "A. hordiq",
            "B. sarguzasht",
            "C. maroq",
            "D. sayir"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "to approach",
        answer: "A. yaqinlashmoq",
        options: [
            "A. yaqinlashmoq",
            "B. harakat qilmoq",
            "C. jo'namoq",
            "D. bormoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "carefully",
        answer: "D. ehtiyotkorlik bilan",
        options: [
            "A. tez",
            "B. sekin",
            "C. katta",
            "D. ehtiyotkorlik bilan"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "a chemical",
        answer: "C. kimyoviy modda",
        options: [
            "A. kimyogar",
            "B. kimyo kitobi",
            "C. kimyoviy modda",
            "D. kimyo"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "to create",
        answer: "B. yaratmoq",
        options: [
            "A. buzmoq",
            "B. yaratmoq",
            "C. o'zgartirmoq",
            "D. yaxshilamoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "evil",
        answer: "A. yomon",
        options: [
            "A. yomon",
            "B. yaxshi",
            "C. qo'rqinchli",
            "D. xayrli"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "experiment",
        answer: "B. tajriba",
        options: [
            "A. baholash",
            "B. tajriba",
            "C. o'lchash",
            "D. o'rganish"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "to kill",
        answer: "C. o'ldirmoq",
        options: [
            "A. yashirmoq",
            "B. tashlanmoq",
            "C. o'ldirmoq",
            "D. qo'rqitmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "laboratory",
        answer: "D. laboratoriya",
        options: [
            "A. laborant",
            "B. ilm-fan",
            "C. natija",
            "D. laboratoriya"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "laugh",
        answer: "B. kulgi",
        options: [
            "A. ohang",
            "B. kulgi",
            "C. shovqin",
            "D. ovoz"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "loud",
        answer: "C. baland",
        options: [
            "A. past",
            "B. yoqimsiz",
            "C. baland",
            "D. qo'rqinchli"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "nervous",
        answer: "A. xavotirlangan",
        options: [
            "A. xavotirlangan",
            "B. qo'rqinchli",
            "C. ayanchli",
            "D. shovqinli"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "noise",
        answer: "C. shovqin",
        options: [
            "A. kulgi",
            "B. ovoz",
            "C. shovqin",
            "D. ohang"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "project",
        answer: "B. yumush",
        options: [
            "A. ish",
            "B. yumush",
            "C. harakat",
            "D. natija"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "to scare",
        answer: "D. qo'rqitmoq",
        options: [
            "A. urushmoq",
            "B. baqirmoq",
            "C. hujum qilmoq",
            "D. qo'rqitmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "secret",
        answer: "C. sir",
        options: [
            "A. sehr",
            "B. masala",
            "C. sir",
            "D. javob"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "to shout",
        answer: "A. baqirmoq",
        options: [
            "A. baqirmoq",
            "B. urushmoq",
            "C. qo'rqitmoq",
            "D. hujum qilmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "to smell",
        answer: "D. hidlamoq",
        options: [
            "A. sezmoq",
            "B. his qilmoq",
            "C. ko'rmoq",
            "D. hidlamoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "terrible",
        answer: "B. juda yomon",
        options: [
            "A. hunuk",
            "B. juda yomon",
            "C. qo'rqinchli",
            "D. hayratlanarli"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "worse",
        answer: "C. yomonroq",
        options: [
            "A. baxil",
            "B. yomon",
            "C. yomonroq",
            "D. juda yomon"
        ]
    }
]
